

Dilpreet Kaur

Personal Support Worker

Contact

Brampton, ON +1 (437) 299-9608 dilpreetdullat39@gmail.com Willing to relocate

Education

PSW - Conestoga College BSc Vet Sci - GADVASU

Certifications

First Aid & CPR **BLS** Certified Ontario Security License G2 Driver's License

1 Save as PDF



Profile Summary

Dedicated PSW with strong care and clinical skills. Specialized in elder care, crisis intervention, medication assistance, and promoting independence. Known for patience, empathy, and resident advocacy.

X Core Competencies

Resident-centered care Mobility Assistance

ADLs Infection Control **GPA Techniques**

PointClickCare Palliative Care

Experience

Health Care Aide - Home Instead (Sep 2024 -Present)

- Delivered personal hygiene care, transport and meal assistance to elderly clients.
- Planned care routines with families and ensured 95%+ satisfaction.

PSW - Amica Senior Lifestyles (Jul 2024 - Aug 2024)

- Supported 12 residents with medication, hygiene, mobility and meals daily.
- Created safe, clean spaces adhering to sanitation standards.

PSW - Schlegel Villages, Guelph (May 2024 -Jul 2024)

 Provided ADL support and designed nutritional care plans in LTC setting.



Volunteer Experience

Community Support Volunteer – Brampton (2023 – 2024)

- Assisted with food distribution and emotional support for unhoused community members.
- Organized social activities to foster inclusion and reduce isolation.